https://www.filesanywhere.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
FilesAnywhere Privacy Policy
Your privacy is our top priority
In today's cloud environment, we understand the importance of protecting our customer's privacy. You can rest assured that FilesAnywhere is committed to safeguarding your data and personal information. Below describes how we collect, use, and handle your personal information when you use our services.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
FilesAnywhere Accounts: In order to setup and service your account, we do require your name, email address, billing address, credit card number and expiration date. Your personal information is always transmitted using SSL protection and stored in an encrypted format.
FilesAnywhere Services: When sending files and messages through our services, we ask for your email address, as well as that of the recipient, in order to complete your request. We maintain this information on our servers in order for you to use.  We will never send promotional emails to, or disclose recipient email addresses, without your permission.
Contests and Promotions: Please be advised that if you request information, sign up for an optional service, submit feedback, or enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and email address so that we may contact you. We may also use the collected information to notify you about important changes regarding our service functionality or related news that you may find useful.
Announcements and Special Offers: If you prefer not to receive announcements or special offers from FilesAnywhere, you may opt out at any time. Simply visit this page to change your email preferences. It's important that you ensure the accuracy of your profile information, including a valid email address so that we may contact you in regard to official changes in our privacy policies should they occur.
Device Information: We collect information from and about the devices you use to access our service. This includes IP addresses, the type of browser, the device you use, and identifiers associated with your devices.
Cookies: Small pieces of data stored in temporary hard drive files by your browser are called cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies and FilesAnywhere’s website login requires the use of cookies. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide special features, such as default login, and to store temporary session data between visits.
Information Protection
Personal Information: FilesAnywhere uses state-of-the-art security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of any personal information that we collect and store. Our Infrastructure team scans the system nightly testing for vulnerabilities. All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access at our SOC II and III certified data center. Our facility is located in Carrollton, Texas and provides multiple security levels and solid reliability.
Files and Data: FilesAnywhere stores all data on an encrypted enterprise grade storage system.  You may also opt to use SSL login for fully encrypted communications with our servers. The use of SSL technology ensures that all data transmitted between the web server and browser remains encrypted.  Additionally, on Professional accounts, your account is password protected with the option for MFA as an added layer of security.
FilesAnywhere Employees: FilesAnywhere is devoted to keeping the content of your files private and secure. Only a few dedicated network technicians on duty at the data center have access to the secure files storage system. Technicians are not permitted to access customer documents unless required by law, and are bound by confidentiality agreements for your protection.
Information Disclosure to Outside Parties
Statistics: Though FilesAnywhere monitors customer traffic patterns and site usage for development of the user interface, along with collecting statistics for performance measurement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise provide your personal information, including your email address, to any outside party.
Surveys: At any time, FilesAnywhere may conduct customer satisfaction surveys for internal use, and only for the benefit of our users. Surveys are only conducted by FilesAnywhere employees.
Government Request: All government data requests are limited in the specific information they seek for an individual and only for court ordered investigations.  We will not provide data to any blanket requests by any government entity.
Consent: By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of basic information as described herein. FilesAnywhere reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy without notice. At a minimum, Privacy Policy changes will post on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how it's used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed.
Rights to Access and Control Your Personal Information: We recommend that you check the accuracy of your personal information from time to time in order to make sure we have the ability to contact you.  This can be done by logging into your account, going to the account profile and making the necessary changes to your personal data.  If you would like for us to send you a copy of your personal data please contact us.  If you terminate your account with us for any reason we will maintain your information for 30 days.  After 30 days, your information will be purged from our servers and will no longer be available.
Still Have Questions?
If you need help or have additional questions regarding the security and use of your personal information, please contact us.
Posted:  5-25-2018
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Privacy PolicyCookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
